So now we've talked about in our restaurant situation how to order food.
所以现在我们已经在我们餐厅的情况下讨论了如何点餐。
We've talked about how to make a reservation how to tell the host or hostess how many people are going
我们已经讨论了如何预订如何告诉主人或女主人有多少人要去
to sit at your table and how to ask for a menu how to get a wine list how to do all that stuff before
坐在你的餐桌旁 如何询问菜单 如何获得酒单 如何做之前的所有事情
you order including getting a suggestion.
您订购，包括获得建议。
Talked about a couple of important words we need to know.
谈到了我们需要知道的几个重要词。
And now we need to actually go through an order it's actually pretty simple.
现在我们需要实际执行一个订单，这实际上非常简单。
When we went through the phrases at the beginning of the class we we talked about a few things that
当我们在课堂开始时浏览这些短语时，我们谈到了一些事情
you can use to request something and we'll see those.
你可以用来请求一些东西，我们会看到的。
In this example.
在这个例子中。
So let's go through this example.
所以让我们来看看这个例子。
This is me ordering a pizza from a waitress.
这是我从女服务员那里点披萨。
OK I guess I'll have a small garden pizza without onions.
好的，我想我要一个没有洋葱的小花园披萨。
THAT MEANS THERE'S THIS PIZZA.
这意味着有这个披萨。
IT'S CALLED THE GARDEN pizza.
它被称为花园披萨。
And it has onions but I don't want the onions all the small garden Pizza the other sizes are probably
它有洋葱，但我不想要洋葱所有的小花园披萨其他尺寸可能是
medium and large of a small garden pizza without onions.
中型和大型的没有洋葱的小花园披萨。
And I'd like extra cheese.
我想要额外的奶酪。
I'd like.
我想要。
Remember.
记住。
I'd like add cheese please.
我想加奶酪。
More cheese.
更多奶酪。
There's already cheese I want more.
已经有我想要更多的奶酪了。
Give me more cheese OK.
再给我点奶酪就好了。
Oh could you also please add sun dried tomatoes to half sun dried tomatoes.
哦，你能把晒干的西红柿加到半晒干的西红柿里吗？
Are there sun dried tomatoes.
有晒干的西红柿吗？
There tomatoes that sit in the sun.
有坐在阳光下的西红柿。
They're delicious.
它们很好吃。
If you haven't had those on pizza you've got to try it.
如果你还没有在披萨上吃过那些，你必须尝试一下。
You don't get anything else from this course.
你不会从这门课程中得到任何其他东西。
Hopefully the recommendation about sun dried tomatoes will be something you try.
希望关于晒干西红柿的推荐会是你尝试的。
I'd like to add sun dried tomatoes 2 1/2.
我想加入晒干的西红柿 2 1/2。
OK.
好的。
So I only want it on this part this part not the whole thing.
所以我只想要这部分而不是整个部分。
And then I'll have I'll have a side salad as well a side salad.
然后我要一份沙拉和一份沙拉。
That's a smaller salad.
那是一个较小的沙拉。
If it's just a salad maybe that's my whole meal.
如果只是沙拉，那可能就是我的全餐。
That's my main food right my main course side.
那是我的主要食物，就在我的主菜方面。
So it comes with the pizza.
所以它与披萨一起出现。
OK.
好的。
Then the waitress says what kind of dressing on the salad.
然后女服务员说沙拉上放什么样的调料。
What kind of dressing on the salad.
沙拉上有什么调料。
Remember I mentioned dressing comes with a salad.
记得我提到过沙拉配沙拉。
It's on a salad.
它在沙拉上。
I'll have thousand island Thousand Island.
我将拥有千岛千岛。
And I also don't want onions on my salad.
我也不想在沙拉上放洋葱。
So usually a salad will come with red onions maybe I don't want onions.
所以通常沙拉会配红洋葱，也许我不想要洋葱。
In fact I actually like onions and I would never order extra cheese and I would never order a Thousand
事实上，我真的很喜欢洋葱，我永远不会点额外的奶酪，我永远不会点一千个
Island.
岛。
I just made this example.
我刚刚做了这个例子。
And when I made this example I was I became someone else.
当我做这个例子时，我变成了另一个人。
OK I'll have Thousand Island.
好的，我将拥有千岛。
It's orange.
它是橙色的。
Thousand Island is orange.
千岛是橙色的。
It's a kind of dressing.
这是一种装扮。
Very popular.
很受欢迎。
I have Thousand Island.
我有千岛。
And I also don't want onions on my salad.
我也不想在沙拉上放洋葱。
Sure no problem.
好没问题。
That's a way to recognize what I said.
这是一种认可我所说的话的方式。
That lets me know that she heard what I said.
这让我知道她听到了我说的话。
She's writing it down on her little book tour no problem.
她在她的小书之旅上写下来没问题。
Anything else.
还要别的吗。
Whenever you want to know if somebody wants more stuff after they've already told you two or three or
每当你想知道某人在告诉你两三个或之后是否想要更多东西时
four or five things.
四五个事物。
The best phrase you can use is anything else.
您可以使用的最佳短语是其他任何东西。
Can I have a Coca-Cola.
我可以喝可口可乐吗？
Anything else.
还要别的吗。
Can I have some chocolate.
我可以吃点巧克力吗？
Sure.
当然。
Anything else.
还要别的吗。
I have a coffee.
我有一杯咖啡。
OK.
好的。
Anything else you can say it Forever Forever.
任何其他你可以说它永远永远。
It's a pretty polite phrase as well.
也是很客气的一句话。
It's just a way to say I'm ready if you want to tell me you want more stuff.
如果你想告诉我你想要更多东西，这只是一种说我准备好了的方式。
OK.
好的。
Sure no problem.
好没问题。
Anything else.
还要别的吗。
Will that be all means the same thing but it's a little bit more formal.
这是否都意味着同样的事情，但它更正式一点。
Will that be all.
就这些吧。
It's kind of expecting me to say Yes I'm finished.
有点期待我说是的，我已经完成了。
Anything else is kind of open like I have no idea.
其他任何东西都是开放的，就像我不知道一样。
Maybe you do want more.
也许你确实想要更多。
Right.
正确的。
So they're kind of the same in this situation but they feel different.
所以他们在这种情况下是一样的，但他们感觉不同。
Will that be all.
就这些吧。
Expects me to be finished.
期待我完蛋。
Anything else makes me feel like well when I'll also have the catch of the day Catch of the day.
其他任何事情都会让我感觉良好，因为我也将获得当日的渔获。
Fish and pizza together.
鱼和披萨一起吃。
That's very strange.
这很奇怪。
OK.
好的。
That's all for now.
目前为止就这样了。
Again we use this to let the waiter or waitress know that we might order something else later.
我们再次使用它来让服务员或女服务员知道我们稍后可能会订购其他东西。
In this case probably dessert we might order dessert later.
在这种情况下，可能是甜点，我们稍后可能会点甜点。
So that's it.
就是这样了。
That's how you order we used some of the phrases we learned at the beginning of class as well as a few
这就是您订购的方式，我们使用了我们在课堂开始时学到的一些短语以及一些
of the words we went over.
我们过去的话。
And it's pretty simple but if you do it enough times you'll get the feeling for how many different ways
这很简单，但如果你做的次数足够多，你就会感觉到有多少种不同的方法
you can put these phrases together.
你可以把这些短语放在一起。
And I want to show you at least one so that you can you know you can really kind of feel it.
我想至少给你看一个，这样你就可以知道你真的能感觉到它。
I think that's an important part of learning a language.
我认为这是学习语言的重要组成部分。
It's not only about learning grammar and rules and words.
这不仅仅是学习语法、规则和单词。
You also have to kind of feel it because language especially using spoken language is very cultural.
您还必须有一种感觉，因为语言，尤其是使用口语的语言非常具有文化性。
It's really related to the culture.
这真的和文化有关。
The culture happens sort of within situations at a restaurant.
这种文化发生在餐厅的情境中。
So you've got to try to figure feel how these are used naturally.
所以你必须试着去感受这些是如何自然使用的。
I'm trying to get these across but I hope you can actually try to use them.
我正在尝试解决这些问题，但我希望您实际上可以尝试使用它们。
So go to go to a restaurant order something in English and try them out try it out play with it.
所以去一家餐馆用英语点一些东西，然后试一试，试一试。